Edward Twitchell Hall papers 1930-1979
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series III: Writings, 1935-1979
  - Beyond Culture: Original Manuscript, Chapter 3-4. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Beyond Culture: Original Manuscript, Chapter 5. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Beyond Culture: Original Manuscript, Chapter 6. (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Beyond Culture: Original Manuscript, Chapter 7. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Beyond Culture: Original Manuscript, Chapter 8. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Beyond Culture: Original Manuscript, Chapter 9. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Beyond Culture: Chapter 10. (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Beyond Culture: Chapter 11. (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Beyond Culture: Chapter 12. (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Beyond Culture: Chapter 12 (13?). (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Beyond Culture: Chapter 14. (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Beyond Culture: Chapter 15. (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Table of Contents and Introduction. 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 1. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 2. (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 3. (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 4. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 5. (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 6. (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 7. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 8. (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 9. (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 10. (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 11. (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 12. (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 13. (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 14. (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 15. (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 16. (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Beyond Culture(Early Version): Chapter 17. (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Introduction Missing, Chapter 1. (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Chapter 2. (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version):: Chapter 3. (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version):: Chapter 4. (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Chapter 5. (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Chapter 6. (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Chapter 7. (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Beyond Culture: First Intermediate Version): Chapter 8. (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Chapter 9. (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Chapter 10. (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Chapter 11. (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Chapter 12. (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Chapter 13. (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Chapter 14. (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Chapter 15. (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Chapter 16. (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Beyond Culture First Intermediate Version): Bibliography. (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Introduction (Chapter 1 and Bibligraphy missing). (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 2. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 3. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 4. (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 5. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 6. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 7. (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 8. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 9. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 10. (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 11. (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 12. (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 13. (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 14. (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 15. (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Beyond Culture (Second Intermediate Verson): Chapter 16. (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy to be thrown out when original is returned by Doubleday, April): Acknowledgments, Author's Preface, Dedication, Table of Contents. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Introduction. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 1. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 2. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 3. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 4. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 5. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 6. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 7. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 8. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 9. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 10. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 11. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 12. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 13. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 14. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Chapter 15. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Bibliographies. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Beyond Culture (Last Working Copy): Indexes. 1975 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Beyond Culture: English Edition. Anchor Press/Doubleday, Garden City, New York. 1976 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Beyond Culture: English Edition. Anchor Books, Anchor Press/Doubleday, Garden City, New York. 1977 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Beyond Culture: English Edition. Kensyusha, Tokyo, (Introduction and Chapters 1, 2, 14, 15 edited with notes by Tesuo Anzai). No Date (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Beyond Culture: French Edition. (Au-Delà de a Culture), Éditions du Seuil, Paris, Galleys, Chapters 1-4. 1979 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Beyond Culture: French Edition. (Au-Delà de a Culture), Éditions du Seuil, Paris, Chapters 5-9. 1979 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Beyond Culture: French Edition. (Au-Delà de a Culture), Éditions du Seuil, Paris, Chapters 10--. 1979 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Beyond Culture: Japanese Edition, no publisher. No Date (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Papers, Articles: "Cultural Models in Transcultural Communication." 1976/1979 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Papers, Articles: ETH Quotes. 1976 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Papers, Articles:"Human Needs for Autonomy and Dependence in Technological Environments." 1977 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Papers, Articles: "Nonverbal Communication for Educators." 1977 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Papers, Articles: ETH Quotes. 1977 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Papers, Articles: "Department of Ignorance: the Remarkable Thermal Qualities of the Human Skin or Burning Down the House to Cook the Pig." 1978 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Papers, Articles: "Prospects for Improving Human Relations Overseas." 1978 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Papers, Articles: ETH Quotes. 1978 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Papers, Articles: "Let's Heat People Instead of Houses." 1979 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Papers, Articles: "The Role of Industrial Design in Community Development: An Anthropological View." 1979 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Papers, Articles: ETH Quotes. 1979 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Papers, Articles: "Adumbrative Processes in Inter-Ethnic Encounters." No Date (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Papers, Articles: "Some Tension Points between Arabs and Americans." No Date (Box 58, Folder 13)